illusivelondon.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy

Illusive London Privacy Policy 

At Illusive London We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

Our website uses cookies. We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first register to our website. / By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

**What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Contact details, such as, Name, email, telephone number, Home/Billing address
  * Account information, password and log in details.
  * Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation)
  * Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters
  * Any other information that you choose to send to us

**What** **do we do with your data? Using your personal information**

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. 

We may use your personal information to:

  * Administer the website.
  * Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.
  * Enable your use of the services available on the website.
  * Send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website.
  * Send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you.
  * Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications
  * Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested
  * Send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)
  * Provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user.
  * Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website
  * Keep the website secure and prevent fraud.
  * We may, from time to time, use your personal information to administer a prize draw or competition but this will only happen if you have chosen to enter

As part of our marketing programme, we may pool and share aggregated data with third parties. We then use this data to produce statistics about our customers. This helps us to select and tailor products, services or special discounts to you and to inform you about those which we think you will be interested to hear about - This information will not be used to identify any individual user.

**For General Research and Analysis Purposes**  

We use data about how our visitors use our Sites, Apps and Services to understand customer behavior or preferences.  For example, we may use information about how visitors to Illusive London search for and find products to better understand the best ways to organize and present product offerings in our storefront. 

**Sharing Your Data**

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

Third party service providers processing personal data on Illusive London’s behalf, for example to process credit cards and payments, shipping and deliveries, manage and service our data, distribute emails, research and analysis, manage brand and product promotions as well as administering certain services and features. 

All of our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, sage pay. You can review the sage pay privacy policy at www.sagepay.com. We will share information with sage pay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.

Illusive London will periodically audit the use of data by any third parties to which it shares your information

**Cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; keep track of items in your shopping basket; prevent fraud and increase website security. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; keep track of your preferences in relation to the use of our website.

Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.

Our advertising services providers may send you cookies for the purpose of enabling the service of advertisements based on your previous visits to our website.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

**Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate; in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

**Security of your personal information**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

**Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

**Your rights related to your personal data:  **

You have the right to request: 

(i) Access to your personal data; 

(ii) The correction of your personal data if it is incomplete or inaccurate; 

(iii) The deletion of your personal data. 

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:

  * The extent that we are required to do so by law
  * In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings
  * In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)
  * To the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and
  * To any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.
  * The supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

Where we have obtained your consent for the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data, including opting-out from the use for direct marketing purposes. 

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law. You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes, by sending an email to us at [Mail@IllusiveLondon.com](mailto:Mail@IllusiveLondon.com).

We will ask you to agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes. We will also provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes. Any such transfer of your personal data will be carried out in compliance with applicable laws and we will treat the information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy Statement. 

**KLARNA**

We work with Klarna AB Klarna AB (“Klarna”) is a provider of financial services. Klarna's principal place of business is at Sveavägen 46, 111 34 Stockholm, Sweden. Klarna is registered with the Swedish companies register under the registration number 556737-0431 and licensed by and under the supervision of the Swedish Financial Supervisory Authority (www.fi.se), Box 7821, 10397 Stockholm, Sweden, and the Swedish Data Protection Authority (http://www.datainspektionen.se/in-english/), Box 8114, 10420 Stockholm, Sweden.

We need to provide Klarna with certain information about you and the order to enable Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their credit products. We need to transfer to Klarna account details such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and payment history, as well as your order details, such as payment method, shipping details, what was ordered, and similar. This will not be done if you do not select Klarna as your payment method. The further use of this data will be governed by [Klarna’s Privacy Policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy).

**Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

To modify your email subscriptions or to opt-out of receiving Illusive London communication(s), please log into your Illusive London account and modify your preferences in the "My Details" section of our website.  

To opt out of the Illusive London basket reminder emails please follow the link on the bottom of the basket reminder email. 

To opt out of the Illusive London SMS’s please text ILLUSIVESTOP to 62277

You can also contact us to exercise your rights related to your personal data via the email address mail@IllusiveLondon.com

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to mail@IllusiveLondon.com or by post to 

DBS Clothing LTD, 

Unit 8A Plaxton Park, 

Cayton Low Road, 

Scarborough. 

North Yorkshire

YO11 3BQ

**Terms of Use**

**Introduction**

These terms of use govern your use of our website; by using our website, you accept these terms of use in full. If you disagree with these terms of use or any part of these terms of use, you must not use our website.

If you register with our website we will ask you to expressly agree to these terms of use.

You are only eligible to use the Platform if you are of legal age in your country or if you have consent from your parent or guardian.  There may be certain age restrictions for specific Platform services in various countries.

Our website uses cookies. By using our website and agreeing to these terms of use, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy / cookies policy.

**Licence to use website**

Unless otherwise stated, we or our licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. 

Subject to the licence below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved. You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms of use.

You must not:

  * Republish material from this website (including republication on another website)
  * Sell, rent or sub-license material from the website
  * Show any material from the website in public
  * Reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for a commercial purpose
  * Edit or otherwise modify any material on the website
  * Redistribute material from this website except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution (such as our newsletter).

Where content is specifically made available for redistribution, it may only be redistributed within your organisation. 

**Acceptable use**

You must not use our website in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity.

You must not use our website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.

You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to our website without our express written consent.

**Products**

The advertising of products on our website constitutes an “invitation to treat” - not a contractual offer.

Prices stated on our website may be stated incorrectly – We reserve the right to amend Prices at any time.

The purchase of products via our website will be subject to our Terms of Sale.

We will ask you to agree to our terms of sale each time you purchase a product or products via our website.

**Product Reviews**

In these terms of use, “your reviews” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to us for publication on our website or social media, whether as a product review or otherwise.

You grant to us a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free licence to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your reviews in any existing or future media. You also grant to us the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights.

You warrant and represent that your reviews will comply with these terms of use.

Your reviews must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party's legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or us or a third party (in each case under any applicable law and in any jurisdiction).

Your reviews (and their publication on our website) must not:

  * Be libellous or maliciously false;
  * Be obscene or indecent;
  * Infringe any copyright, moral right, database right, trade mark right, design right, right in passing off, or other intellectual property right;
  * Infringe any right of confidence, right of privacy, or right under data protection legislation;
  * Constitute negligent advice or contain any negligent statement;
  * Constitute an incitement to commit a crime;
  * Be in contempt of any court, or in breach of any court order;
  * Be in breach of racial or religious hatred or discrimination legislation;
  * Be blasphemous;
  * Be in breach of official secrets legislation;
  * Be in breach of any contractual obligation owed to any person;
  * Be untrue, false, inaccurate or misleading;
  * Consist of or contain any instructions, advice or other information which may be acted upon and could, if acted upon, cause illness, injury or death, or any other loss or damage;
  * Constitute spam;
  * Be offensive, deceptive, threatening, abusive, harassing, or menacing, hateful, discriminatory or inflammatory; or
  * Cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety to any person.

Your reviews must be appropriate, civil, tasteful and accord with generally accepted standards of etiquette and behaviour on the internet.

You must not use any review to link to any website or web page consisting of or containing material that would, were it posted on our website, breach the provisions of these terms of use.

You must not submit any reviews to the website that are or have ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint.

We reserve the right to edit or remove any reviews submitted to our website, or stored on our servers, or hosted or published upon our website.

Notwithstanding our rights under these terms of use in relation to your reviews, we do not undertake to monitor the submission of reviews to, or the publication of reviews on, our website.

**Limited Warranties**

Whilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up-to-date.

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to this website and the use of this website (including, without limitation, any warranties implied by law of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and/or the use of reasonable care and skill).

**Limitations and Exclusions of Liability**

Nothing in these terms of use will: (a) limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence; (b) limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; (c) limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or (d) exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law. If you are a consumer, any statutory rights that you have, that cannot be excluded or limited, will not be affected by these terms of use.

The limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section and elsewhere in these terms of use: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the terms of use or in relation to the subject matter of the terms of use, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty.

To the extent that the website and the information and services on the website are provided free-of-charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.

We will not be liable to you in respect of any business losses, including (without limitation) loss of or damage to profits, income, revenue, use, production, anticipated savings, business, contracts, commercial opportunities or goodwill.

**Indemnity**

You hereby indemnify us and undertake to keep us indemnified against any losses, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including without limitation legal expenses and any amounts paid by us to a third party in settlement of a claim or dispute on the advice of our legal advisers) incurred or suffered by us arising out of any breach by you of any provision of these terms of use, or arising out of any claim that you have breached any provision of these terms of use.

**Breaches of these terms of use;**

Without prejudice to our other rights under these terms of use, if you breach these terms of use in any way, or if we reasonably suspect that you have breached these terms of use in any way, we may:

  * Send you one or more formal warnings;
  * Temporarily suspend your access to the website;
  * Permanently prohibit you from accessing the website;
  * Block computers using your IP address from accessing the website;
  * Contact your internet services provider and request that they block your access to the website;
  * Bring court proceedings against you for breach of contract or otherwise; and/or
  * Suspend and/or delete your account with the website.

**Variation**

We may revise these terms of use from time-to-time. Revised terms of use will apply to the use of our website from the date of the publication of the revised terms of use on our website. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.

**Assignment**

We may transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with our rights and/or obligations under these terms of use without notifying you or obtaining your consent. You may not transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these terms of use.

**Severability**

If a provision of these terms of use is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.

**Exclusion of third party rights**

These terms of use are for the benefit of you and us, and are not intended to benefit any third party or be enforceable by any third party. The exercise of our and your rights in relation to these terms of use is not subject to the consent of any third party.

**Entire Agreement**

These terms of use, together with our privacy policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.

**Law and Jurisdiction**

These terms of use will be governed by and construed in accordance with English law, and any disputes relating to these terms of use will be subject to the [non-]exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales.

**Company details**

The full name of our company is DBS ONLINE LTD.

Our Company number is: 08457731

Our address is:

Illusive London

Unit 8A Plaxton Park

Cayton Low Road

Scarborough

England

YO11 3BQ

You can contact us by email to mail@IllusiveLondon.com
